{"data":[{"question":"Modern industrial methods have supplanted individual crafts, ________ stone carvers, coopers, and cobblers virtually extinct.","a":"make blacksmiths,","b":"made blacksmiths,","c":"making them blacksmiths,","d":"making blacksmiths,","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use present participle V-ing\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Not only knowledge and skills, but also attitudes ________ in school for students' future adjustment to society.","a":"when cultivated","b":"cultivated","c":"which need to be cultivated","d":"need to be cultivated","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Need + to Verb.\u00a0\n- Passive voice: need to be + PP.\u00a0\n- This sentence is a single clause- doesn't need a relative pronoun (who\/whom\/which...).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"On Mercator's maps, the far northern and southern polar regions are ________.","a":"greatly exaggerated in area.","b":"exaggerating greatly in area.","c":"greatly exaggerate in area.","d":"great exaggeration in area.","answer":"1","explain":"- Adverbs go before past participles that they modify","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"On the slope of Long's Peak in Colorado ________ the ruin of a gigantic tree.","a":"that lies","b":"lies","c":"where lies","d":"lie","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use inversion with adverbial expressions of place at the beginning","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"________ in Shanghai than in any other city in China.","a":"More people live","b":"More people living","c":"It has more people","d":"More living people","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The earth spins on its axis and ________ 23 hours, 56 minutes and 4.09 seconds for one complete rotation.","a":"need","b":"needed","c":"needing","d":"needs","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Parallel structure with Verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"________ on the environment for the gratification of its needs.","a":"Each organism to depend","b":"Every organism depends","c":"All organisms depending","d":"Many organisms can depend","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O. (we need the subject and the verb to make a complete sentence)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Of Charles Dickens' many novels, expectations perhaps ________ to many readers.","a":"the most satisfying one","b":"most satisfying one","c":"more than satisfying one","d":"the more satisfying than","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use the superlative form of long adjective satisfying","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"________, the nation's capital remained in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.","a":"While designing Washington, D.C.","b":"Washington, D.C., was designed","c":"While Washington, D.C., was being designed","d":"Washington, D.C., designed","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice: used when you want to emphasize the person or thing acted on.\u00a0\n- While: is complemented by a clause with an activity that occurs during or at the same time as another activity.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Children learn primarily by ________ the world around them.","a":"experiencing directly of","b":"experience direct","c":"directly physical experience","d":"direct physical experience of","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A gerund goes after a preposition (by + V-ing)\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}